[{
    "category": "cabeca",
    "title": "Question 1",
    "question": "The skull is subdivided into two parts, which are:",
    "answers": ["d"],
    "options": [{
            "label": "Anterior face of the skull and posterior face of the skull",
            "value": "a"
        },{
            "label": "Skull and jaw",
            "value": "b"
        },{
            "label": "Neurocranium and anterior skull",
            "value": "c"
        },{
            "label": "Neurocranium and skeleton of the face",
            "value": "d"
        }
    ]
},{
    "category": "cabeca",
    "title": "Question 2",
    "question": "The neurocranium, in adults, is formed by eight bones, which are:",
    "answers": ["b"],
    "options": [{
            "label": "Frontal, parietal, even temporal, even occipital, sphenoid and ethmoid",
            "value": "a"
        },{
            "label": "A frontal, even parietal, even temporal, an occipital, a sphenoid and an ethmoid",
            "value": "b"
        },{
            "label": "Frontal, parietal, temporal, even occipitals, even sphenoids and an ethmoid",
            "value": "c"
        },{
            "label": "Frontal, parietal, temporal, occipital, even sphenoids, and even ethmoids",
            "value": "d"
        }
    ]
},{
    "category": "cabeca",
    "title": "Question 3",
    "question": "The skeleton of the face consists of 14 irregular bones, which are:",
    "answers": ["a"],
    "options": [{
            "label": "Lacrimal (02), nasal (02), jaw (02), zygomatic (02), palatal (02), inferior nasal concha (02), mandible (01) and vomer (01)",
            "value": "a"
        },{
            "label": "Lacrimal (02), nasal (02), jaw (02), zygomatic (01), palatal (01), inferior nasal concha (02), mandible (02) and vomer (02)",
            "value": "b"
        },{
            "label": "Lacrimal (01), nasal (01), jaw (02), zygomatic (02), palatal (03), inferior nasal concha (03), mandible (01) and vomer (01)",
            "value": "c"
        },{
            "label": "Lacrimal (02), nasal (02), jaw (02), zygomatic (01), palatal (02), inferior nasal concha (02), mandible (02) and vomer (01)",
            "value": "d"
        }
    ]
},{
    "category": "cabeca",
    "title": "Question 4",
    "question": "Which of the following sutures does not correspond to a skull suture?",
    "answers": ["d"],
    "options": [{
            "label": "Sagittal suture",
            "value": "a"
        },{
            "label": "Lambdoid suture",
            "value": "b"
        },{
            "label": "Coronal suture",
            "value": "c"
        },{
            "label": "Horizontal suture",
            "value": "d"
        }
    ]
},{
    "category": "cabeca",
    "title": "Question 5",
    "question": "From the anatomical reference points below, mark the alternative that corresponds to an anatomical point of the skull:",
    "answers": ["b"],
    "options": [{
            "label": "Xifoidal",
            "value": "a"
        },{
            "label": "Vertex",
            "value": "b"
        },{
            "label": "Trochanteric",
            "value": "c"
        },{
            "label": "Styloid",
            "value": "d"
        }
    ]
},{
    "category": "cabeca",
    "title": "Question 6",
    "question": "From the bone reference points of the skull below, mark the one that corresponds to the junction of the greater sphenoid wing, scaly part of the temporal, frontal and parietal and that overlaps the anterior division path of the meningeal artery:",
    "answers": ["d"],
    "options": [{
            "label": "Bregma",
            "value": "a"
        },{
            "label": "Asterium",
            "value": "b"
        },{
            "label": "Lambda",
            "value": "c"
        },{
            "label": "Pterium",
            "value": "d"
        }
    ]
},{
    "category": "cabeca",
    "title": "Question 7",
    "question": "The Turkish saddle consists of 03 parts, which are:",
    "answers": ["c"],
    "options": [{
            "label": "Upper portion of the saddle, lower portion of the saddle and central portion of the saddle",
            "value": "a"
        },{
            "label": "Front face of the saddle, rear face of the saddle and inner face of the saddle",
            "value": "b"
        },{
            "label": "Saddle tubercle, pituitary fossa and saddle dorsum",
            "value": "c"
        },{
            "label": "Saddle tubercle, anterior portion of the saddle and posterior portion of the saddle",
            "value": "d"
        }
    ]
},{
    "category": "cabeca",
    "title": "Question 8",
    "question": "About the spinous foramen, it is correct to state that:",
    "answers": ["a"],
    "options": [{
            "label": "It is located posterolateral to the foramen ovale, gives way to the middle meningeal vessels and the meningeal branch of the mandibular nerve",
            "value": "a"
        },{
            "label": "It is located posterolateral to the foramen ovale, and from the passage to the accessory meningeal artery",
            "value": "b"
        },{
            "label": "It is located antero-medial to the foramen ovale, gives way to the middle meningeal vessels and the meningeal branch of the mandibular nerve",
            "value": "c"
        },{
            "label": "It is located antero-medial to the foramen ovale, and from the passage to the accessory meningeal artery",
            "value": "d"
        }
    ]
},{
    "category": "cabeca",
    "title": "Question 9",
    "question": "About the foramen ovale, it is correct to state that:",
    "answers": ["b"],
    "options": [{
            "label": "It is a small foramen, opens superiorly in the supratemporal fossa and gives way to the vagus nerve and the middle meningeal artery",
            "value": "a"
        },{
            "label": "It is a large foramen, opens inferiorly in the infratemporal fossa and gives way to the mandibular nerve (NC V3) and a small accessory meningeal artery",
            "value": "b"
        },{
            "label": "It is a small foramen, opens inferiorly in the infratemporal fossa, and gives way to the mandibular nerve (NC V3) and the middle meningeal artery",
            "value": "c"
        },{
            "label": "It is a large foramen, opens superiorly in the infratemporal fossa, and gives way to the vagus nerve and the middle meningeal artery",
            "value": "d"
        }
    ]
},{
    "category": "cabeca",
    "title": "Question 10",
    "question": "Which nerve is responsible for the innervation of all facial muscles?",
    "answers": ["b"],
    "options": [{
            "label": "Abducent nerve (NC VI)",
            "value": "a"
        },{
            "label": "Facial nerve (NC VII)",
            "value": "b"
        },{
            "label": "Trochlear nerve (NC IV)",
            "value": "c"
        },{
            "label": "Trigeminal nerve (NC V)",
            "value": "d"
        }
    ]
},{
    "category": "cabeca",
    "title": "Question 11",
    "question": "Of the following muscles, which is not part of the face?",
    "answers": ["d"],
    "options": [{
            "label": "Nasal muscle",
            "value": "a"
        },{
            "label": "Mental muscle",
            "value": "b"
        },{
            "label": "Buccinator muscle",
            "value": "c"
        },{
            "label": "Rhomboid muscle",
            "value": "d"
        }
    ]
},{
    "category": "cabeca",
    "title": "Question 12",
    "question": "(ISGH 2018) The main muscles involved with the chewing process are:",
    "answers": ["d"],
    "options": [{
            "label": "Masseter, buccinator, medial pterygoid and lateral pterygoid",
            "value": "a"
        },{
            "label": "Temporal, mouth angle lifter and mouth angle depressor",
            "value": "b"
        },{
            "label": "Masseter, temporal, medial pterygoid and lateral pterygoid",
            "value": "c"
        },{
            "label": "Masseter, temporal, buccinator and medial pterygoid",
            "value": "d"
        }
    ]
},{
    "category": "cabeca",
    "title": "Question 13",
    "question": "The parotid plexus gives rise to five terminal branches of the facial nerve, namely:",
    "answers": ["c"],
    "options": [{
            "label": "Hypoglossal nerve, vagus nerve, zygomatic nerve, trigeminal nerve and glossopharyngeal nerve",
            "value": "a"
        },{
            "label": "Hypoglossal nerve, zygomatic nerve, cervical nerve, abducent nerve and trochlear nerve",
            "value": "b"
        },{
            "label": "Temporal nerve, zygomatic nerve, cheek nerve, marginal jaw nerve, cervical nerve",
            "value": "c"
        },{
            "label": "Temporal nerve, hypoglossal nerve, vagus nerve, abducent nerve and trochlear nerve",
            "value": "d"
        }
    ]
},{
    "category": "cabeca",
    "title": "Question 14",
    "question": "Which of the following arteries is not part of the vascularization of the face?",
    "answers": ["a"],
    "options": [{
            "label": "Obturator artery",
            "value": "a"
        },{
            "label": "Angular artery",
            "value": "b"
        },{
            "label": "Occipital artery",
            "value": "c"
        },{
            "label": "Mental artery",
            "value": "d"
        }
    ]
},{
    "category": "cabeca",
    "title": "Question 15",
    "question": "Of the following bones, which are classified as pneumatic bones?",
    "answers": ["c"],
    "options": [{
            "label": "Zygomatic bone, sphenoid bone, occipital bone, parietal bone and nasal bone",
            "value": "a"
        },{
            "label": "Zygomatic bone, occipital bone, mandibular bone, nasal bone and lacrimal bone",
            "value": "b"
        },{
            "label": "Frontal bone, upper jaw bone, ethmoid bone, sphenoid bone and temporal bone",
            "value": "c"
        },{
            "label": "Frontal bone, nasal bone, ethmoid bone, sphenoid bone and parietal bone",
            "value": "d"
        }
    ]
},{
    "title": "Question 16",
    "question": "Of the options below, which one does not correspond to a structure found on the side wall of the cavernous sinus?",
    "answers": ["d"],
    "options": [{
            "label": "Oculomotor nerve",
            "value": "a"
        },{
            "label": "Trochlear nerve",
            "value": "b"
        },{
            "label": "Trigeminal nerve",
            "value": "c"
        },{
            "label": "Abducent nerve",
            "value": "d"
        }
    ]
},{
    "category": "cabeca",
    "title": "Question 17",
    "question": "The brain is composed of:",
    "answers": ["b"],
    "options": [{
            "label": "Brain, cerebellum, and brainstem (midbrain, bridge, and medulla)",
            "value": "a"
        },{
            "label": "Brain, cerebellum and hypothalamus",
            "value": "b"
        },{
            "label": "Brain, hypothalamus and brainstem (midbrain, bridge and medulla)",
            "value": "c"
        },{
            "label": "Brain, bridge, bulb and hypothalamus",
            "value": "d"
        }
    ]
},{
    "category": "cabeca",
    "title": "Question 18",
    "question": "The ventricular system of the brain is composed of:",
    "answers": ["b"],
    "options": [{
            "label": "02 lateral ventricles, 3rd and 4th frontal ventricles and through the midbrain aqueduct",
            "value": "a"
        },{
            "label": "02 lateral ventricles, from the 3rd and 4th median ventricles and through the midbrain aqueduct",
            "value": "b"
        },{
            "label": "02 lateral ventricles, 01 frontal ventricle and 01 occipital ventricle",
            "value": "c"
        },{
            "label": "04 lateral ventricles, 02 frontal ventricles, 02 occipital ventricles and through the midbrain aqueduct",
            "value": "d"
        }
    ]
},{
    "category": "cabeca",
    "title": "Question 19",
    "question": "From the arteries responsible for brain vascularization below, select the one formed by the union of the vertebral arteries:",
    "answers": ["b"],
    "options": [{
            "label": "Anterior Communicating Artery",
            "value": "a"
        },{
            "label": "Basilar Artery",
            "value": "b"
        },{
            "label": "Posterior Cerebral Artery",
            "value": "c"
        },{
            "label": "Internal Carotid Artery",
            "value": "d"
        }
    ]
},{
    "category": "cabeca",
    "title": "Question 20",
    "question": "The arterial circle of the brain, is formed by:",
    "answers": ["d"],
    "options": [{
            "label": "Internal and external carotid arteries, anterior and posterior cerebral arteries and posterior communicating artery",
            "value": "a"
        },{
            "label": "Internal and external carotid arteries, anterior brain arteries, anterior communicating arteries and meningeal arteries",
            "value": "b"
        },{
            "label": "Posterior cerebral arteries, middle meningeal artery, anterior communicating arteries, internal carotid arteries and anterior cerebral arteries",
            "value": "c"
        },{
            "label": "Posterior cerebral arteries, posterior communicating arteries, internal carotid arteries, anterior cerebral arteries, and anterior communicating arteries",
            "value": "d"
        }
    ]
}
]